There's actually one more thing I want to show you before we actually work
在我们实际开始工作并把代码推送至 GitHub 之前
and we push all this wonderful code up to GitHub
我还要向你展示一个东西
in our package dot JSON. I've shown you a little bit of this before,
在我们的 "package.json" 中，我之前向你们展示过一点
but we can add this scripts section to make our lives a lot easier
我们可以添加这个 "scripts" 部分来让许多事变得更简单
and condense all these long tests into a yarn script for us.
而且它可以把这些长测试浓缩为一个 `yarn script`
So usually, what you'll see in common package dot JSON is you'll see a list of these in here
所以通常来说，一般的 "package.json" 里你都可以看到这里有这么一个列表
for people to look and just automatically run,
供人们查看还有自动运行
one of the most common ones is going to be test.
最常见的一种就是 `"test":`
And to run test, we're going to do yarn, hard hat test.
为了运行测试，我们要执行 `yarn hardhat test`
So now instead of running yarn, Hardhead test,
现在，其他人就不再需要执行 `yarn hardhat test`
someone can just come to your package once this is saved and just run yarn test.
而是可以直接来到你的 "package"，只要这里保存了，就可以运行 `yarn test`
And this will grab this test from your script section
接着它就会从 "scripts" 部分获取这个 "test"
and it will run yarn heart at test
并运行 `yarn hardhat test`
and Bada bing, bada boom,
接着，噼里啪啦，嘭
okay, cool. What else do we probably probably want to do in here?
OK 酷~ 我们还要在这里做些什么？
Well, we probably want to have a test staging section
我们大概还需要一个 `"test:staging"` 部分
that'll run yarn Hardhead test dash dash, network Rinkeby.
它运行 `yarn hardhat test --network rinkeby`
I'm not going to run that. But that's probably something we want to have in here,
我并不会运行它，但这里确实需要有它
we're probably going to want some linting.
我们大概还想要有一些 "linting"
So we showed you briefly that linting thing.
之前我向你们简短地展示过一些关于 "linting" 的东西
So we'll have a yarn lint, which will just run yarn, sole hint.
所以我们需要一个 `yarn lint`，它运行 `yarn solhint`
And then we'll just have it so hence the contracts folder. And anything that starts out soul.
我们就让它 solhint 'contracts' 文件夹下所有的 ".sol" 文件
So now if I run yarn, lint,
现在如果我运行 `yarn lint`
it'll run soul hint, and all of our code here
它就会 solhint 我们这里所有的代码
and it'll give us some warnings here, which we can pretty much all ignore.
这里它给了我们一些 "warning"，基本上都可以忽略掉
And Solon actually has an auto fix and auto fix that we can add,
solhint 还有一个自动修复功能，我们也可以添加上
by doing yarn lint fix, we'll say yarn. So hint, contracts slash start out. So we'll do dash dash fix.
需要运行 `yarn lint:fix` 然后是 "yarn solhint 'contracts/*.sol' --fix"
So now we run yarn, lint fix, it'll auto fix, which there's nothing to auto fix.
现在我们运行 `yarn lint:fix` 它就会自动修复，不过也没什么可修复的
So nothing happens. But it's good to have anyways.
所以什么都不会发生，但无论如何还是得有的
And then we can do our formatter,
接着我们可以运行我们的 "formatter"
we're just going to format our code
为的是格式化我们的代码
format, that which will do yarn, prettier, dash dash write to,
`"format": "yarn prettier --write"
and we'll just do a period to do everything.
我们直接写句号(".") 来格式化所有内容
And then we can just do yarn format.
然后我们就可以使用 `yarn format`
And it's gonna fix all of our, it's going to fix everything for us, which is great.
接着它就会处理我们所有的，处理我们所有的内容，非常好
And then we finally can have coverage. By running yarn hardhat coverage,
然后就是最后一个 `"coverage": "yarn hardhat coverage"`
now we can just run yarn coverage, will give us this wonderful little coverage report.
现在我们可以运行 `yarn coverage`，它就会为我们提供一份小而美的 "coverage" 报告
Awesome. So our packages looking fantastic.
太棒了，我们的 "package" 看起来棒极了
Maybe we'll even come into package json.
或许我们甚至可以进入 "package.json"
We'll give this a name. We'll call this hard hat.
给它一个 "name" 就叫 "hardhat fund me"
And me give it an author, which is going to be your name. So I'm just gonna say Patrick Collins,
再给它一个 "author" 也就是你的名字，对我来说就是 "patrick collins"
and we'll give it a version in here. of 1.0 Point
我们再给它一个 `"version": "1.0.0"`
Oh, oops. And let's do icons instead of spaces.
哦，这里要用 "-" 来代替空格
Oh, and one more thing. We're not using ES lint. So all this es lint stuff, we can dump
哦！还有一件事，我们并没有使用 "eslint"，所以所有这些 "eslint" 的东西，我们都可以删掉
and we could delete the yarn dot lock and reinstall. But yeah, whatever.
我们可以删掉 "yarn.lock" 然后再重新安装，不过现在先不管了
We don't have a readme, but that's okay.
我们还没有 "README"，但没关系
If you want to go back, like I said, go check out that best readme template
如果你想的话，就像我说的，去找一下那个最好的 "README" 模板("Best README Template")
and go update your READMEs to make them look as awesome as this, you can do that as well.
然后更新一下你的 "README" 让它看起来和这个一样棒
But other than that, we've got an awesome code repo here.
但除此之外，我们已经有了一个非常棒的代码库了